* Language 
    * English

 



 

 

* EN

    

    

    

    

    

[Home](https://www.stepping-stone.ch/en/ "Home")Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

stepping stone Ltd is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the stepping stone Ltd website and governs data collection and usage. By using the stepping stone Ltd website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

Collection of your Personal Information
---------------------------------------

stepping stone Ltd collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. stepping stone Ltd also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favourites.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by stepping stone Ltd. This information can include: your IP address, operation system, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by stepping stone Ltd for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the stepping stone Ltd website.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through, for example stepping stone Ltd blog comments, this information may be collected and used by others.

stepping stone Ltd is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the stepping stone Ltd and stepping stone Ltd family of websites.

Use of your Personal Information
--------------------------------

stepping stone Ltd collects and uses your personal information to operate the stepping stone AG website and deliver the services you have requested. stepping stone Ltd also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from stepping stone Ltd and its affiliates. stepping stone Ltd may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

stepping stone Ltd does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. stepping stone Ltd may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to stepping stone Ltd, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

stepping stone Ltd does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

stepping stone Ltd keeps track of the websites and pages our customers visit within stepping stone Ltd, in order to determine what stepping stone Ltd services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within stepping stone Ltd to customers whose behaviour indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Disclosure of Personal Information
----------------------------------

stepping stone Ltd will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on stepping stone Ltd or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of stepping stone Ltd; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of stepping stone Ltd, or the public.

Use of Cookies
--------------

The stepping stone Ltd website use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the stepping stone Ltd services or websites you visit.

Use of Social Plugins
---------------------

Our websites use social plugins from sites such as Facebook, Twitter and Xing. The plugins are marked with the provider’s logo, e.g. “Like” buttons.

If you access one of our websites and it contains one of these plugins, the provider will be notified via the plugin that you have accessed our website. If you are logged into the provider’s site at the same time, the provider can match up your visit to your profile. If you interact with the plugins, the corresponding information will be transmitted directly from your browser to the provider and stored there.

If you do not want providers to collect data about you, you can select the “Block cookies from third-party providers” option in your browser settings. If there is embedded content from other providers, the browser will then no longer send corresponding information to that provider’s server. However, in some cases this setting will mean that other content on our website no longer works.

Security of your Personal Information
-------------------------------------

stepping stone Ltd secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. stepping stone Ltd secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

Changes to this Statement
-------------------------

stepping stone Ltd will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. stepping stone Ltd encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how stepping stone Ltd is protecting your information.

Contact Information
-------------------

stepping stone Ltd welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that stepping stone Ltd has not adhered to this Statement, please contact stepping stone Ltd at support(at)stepping-stone.ch. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.

This English version of the privacy policy is a translation of the original German version of the Datenschutzerklärung. If there are any contradictions or inconsistencies between the original German version of the privacy policy and any version or translation of the privacy policy in any other language, the German version of the privacy policy prevail.

In case of doubt, only the original German version [Datenschutzerklärung](https://www.stepping-stone.ch/en/privacy-policy/ "Öffnet internen Link im aktuellen Fenster") is valid.

Berne, May 2018

### stepping stone Ltd – Your Cloud Partner

#### ISO/IEC certifications

#### Products

#### Follow us on

#### Contact

stepping stone Ltd  
Wasserwerkgasse 7  
CH-3011 Bern  
  
Phone: [+41 31 332 53 63](tel:0041313325363)  
  
[info(at)stepping-stone.ch](javascript:linkTo_UnCryptMailto('ocknvq,kphqBuvgrrkpi\/uvqpg0ej');)  

© 2004 - 2024 [stepping stone Ltd](https://www.stepping-stone.ch/en/) | [Imprint](https://www.stepping-stone.ch/en/legal-notice/) | [Terms and Conditions](https://www.stepping-stone.ch/en/terms-and-conditions/) | [Privacy Policy](https://www.stepping-stone.ch/en/privacy-policy/) | [Data Processing Agreement](https://www.stepping-stone.ch/en/data-processing-agreement/)



* Login failed. Please check your user name and password and try again.

* Back
* Forward
* send order
